Espy, Watt; Papers apap301
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Documentation of Executions, 1730-2008; Undated; 2; 44.5 cubic ft.
  - State, 1730-2008; Undated; 2.1
    - Alabama, unconfirmed and possible executions, 1825-1860; Undated (Box 2 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15-16)
    - Alaska, 1879-1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Arizona, A-B, 1910-1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Arizona, B-C, 1916-1998; Undated (Box 2 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Arizona, C-D, 1879-1995; Undated (Box 2 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Arizona, D, 1929-1970; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Arizona, F-G, 1911-1999; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Arizona, H, 1882-1994 (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Arizona, H, J-L, 1934-1999 (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Arizona, L-M, 1897-1996; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Arizona, M-R, 1891-1991; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Arizona, S-U, 1914-1991; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Arizona, V-W, multiple executions, 1922-1999 (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Arizona, executions recorded in city, county, and statewide records, 1968; 1981; 1986; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Arkansas, A-B, 1878-1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Arkansas, B-C, 1886-1982; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Arkansas, C-D, 1893-1997; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Arkansas, D-G, 1881-1995; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Arkansas, H, 1902-1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Arkansas, H-L, 1879-1983; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Arkansas, L-P, 1874-1996; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Arkansas, P-R, 1885-1999; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Arkansas, R-S, 1906-2000; Undated (Box 3 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Arkansas, S, 1909-1995; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Arkansas, S-V, 1893-1990; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Arkansas, W, 1869-1997; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Arkansas, unidentified and multiple executions, 1891-1997; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Arkansas, executions recorded in county and statewide records, 1890-1997; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Arkansas, unconfirmed and possible executions, Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - California, A, 1879-1995 (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - California, A, 1923-1979; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - California, A-B, 1932-1979; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - California, B, 1925-1996; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - California, B, 1913-1996; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - California, B, 1930-1996 (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - California, B, 1916-1955; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - California, B-C, 1906-1964; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - California, C, 1933-1988; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - California, C, 1954-1992; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - California, C, 1884-1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - California, C, 1939-1989; Undated (Box 4 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - California, C, 1949-1994; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - California, C-D, 1939-1989; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - California, D, 1891-1975; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - California, D, 1895-1986 (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - California, D-E, 1937-1962; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - California, E-F, 1854-1968; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - California, F-G, 1856-1987; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - California, G, 1942-1983; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - California, G, 1914-1984; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - California, G-H, 1907-1963; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - California, H, 1989-1992 (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - California, H, 1980-1994 (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - California, H, 1877-1992; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - California, H, 1928-1994; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - California, H-J, 1884-1969; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - California, J-K, 1885-1994; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - California, K, 1924-1976; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - California, K-L, 1929-1980; Undated (Box 5 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - California, L, 1887-1961; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - California, L, 1936-1989 (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - California, L-M, 1885-1995; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - California, M, 1880-2001; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - California, M, 1898-1992; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - California, M-N, 1881-1992; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - California, N-O, 1866-1988; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - California, O-P, 1899-1977; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - California, P, 1864-1980; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - California, P-R, 1918-1987; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - California, R, 1896-1996; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - California, R-S, 1879-1982; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - California, S, 1884-1973; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - California, S, 1885-1969; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - California, S, 1883-1999; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - California, S, 1899-1994; Undated (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - California, T, 1891-1997 (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - California, T-V, 1873-1988 (Box 6 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - California, V-W, 1932-1995; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - California, W, 1884-1996; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - California, W-Z, 1902-1990; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - California, Z, 1953-1964 (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - California, multiple executions, 1929-1983; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - California, multiple executions, 1938-1995; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - California, multiple executions, 1953-1992 (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - California, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1880-1990; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - California, executions recorded in statewide records, 1931-1989; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Colorado, A-C, 1881-1992; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Colorado, D-F, 1932-1997 (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Colorado, G-J, 1886-1994; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Colorado, K-L, 1939-1994; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Colorado, M, 1890-1994; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Colorado, N-R, 1879-1949; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Colorado, S, 1880-1994; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Colorado, S-W, 1883-1986 (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Colorado, multiple executions, 1896-1994; Undated (Box 7 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Colorado, executions recorded in county and statewide records, 1947-1982 (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Connecticut, A-B, 1803-1965; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Connecticut, B-C, 1920-1977; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Connecticut, C, 1894-1985; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Connecticut, C-D, 1749-1989; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Connecticut, D, F-K, 1854-1991; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Connecticut, K-M, 1816-1991; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Connecticut, M-O, 1807-1989; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Connecticut, P-R, 1833-1991; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Connecticut, R-S, 1858-1989; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Connecticut, T,W, Z, 1917-1993; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Connecticut, unidentified and multiple executions, 1918-1951; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Connecticut, executions recorded in city and statewide records, 1981; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Delaware, A-B, 1792-1996; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Delaware, C-D, 1878-1996; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Delaware, G-P, 1915-1992; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Delaware, R-Y, 1850-1996; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Delaware, multiple executions, 1917 (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Delaware, executions recorded in statewide records, 1956-1977; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia, B-H, 1896-1972; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia, M-N, 1886-1976; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia, P-T, 1873-1983 (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia, executions recorded in district wide records, 1989; Undated (Box 8 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 23)
    - Florida, A, 1852-1990; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Florida, A, 1912-1991; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Florida, A-B, 1850-1995; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Florida, B, 1891-1995; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Florida, B, 1833-1995; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Florida, B, 1910-2000; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Florida, B-C, 1887-1996; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Florida, C, 1848-1998; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Florida, C, 1939-1991; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Florida, C, 1916-1991 (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Florida, C-D, 1905-1988; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Florida, D, 1886-1999; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Florida, D, 1982-1986; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Florida, D-E, 1926-1993; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Florida, F, 1901-1991; Undated (Box 9 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Florida, F, 1957-1989 (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Florida, F-G, 1902-1986 (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Florida, G, 1849-1984; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Florida, G-H, 1897-1991; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Florida, H, 1838-1999; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Florida, H, 1897-1991; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Florida, J, 1853-1943; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Florida, J, 1927-1993; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Florida, J-K, 1888-1998; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Florida, L-M, 1894-1974; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Florida, M, 1912-1992; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Florida, M, 1911-1992; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Florida, M-N, 1875-1997; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Florida, N-P, 1894-1995; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Florida, P-Q, 1887-2000; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Florida, R, 1877-1987; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Florida, R-S, 1906-1984; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Florida, S, 1848-2000; Undated (Box 10 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Florida, S, 1895-1998; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Florida, S, 1980-1991; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Florida, T, 1885-1990; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Florida, T, 1986 (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Florida, T-W, 1886-1986; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Florida, W, 1887-1995; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Florida, W-Y, 1869-2002; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Florida, Z and unidentified executions, 1933-2002; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Florida, multiple executions, 1846-1976; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Florida, executions in city and county histories, 1954-1993; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Florida, executions recorded in county histories, 1976-1991 (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Florida, executions recorded in statewide records, 1945-1993 (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Florida, executions recorded in statewide records, Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Florida, unconfirmed and possible executions, 1856-1926; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Georgia, A-B, 1835-2008; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Georgia, B, 1867-1988; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Georgia, B, 1877-1991; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Georgia, B, 1847-1993; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Georgia, C, 1901-1998; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Georgia, C, 1801-1988; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Georgia C, 1819-1991; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Georgia, D, 1878-1995; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 22)
    - Georgia, D, 1858-1964; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 23)
    - Georgia, E, 1821-1973; Undated (Box 11 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 24)
    - Georgia, F-g, 1851-1997 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Georgia, G, 1892-1985; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Georgia, H, 1903-1994 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Georgia, H, 1858-1991; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Georgia, H-I, 1849-2001 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Georgia, J, 1833-1991; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Georgia, J, 1884-1991; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Georgia, K-L, 1884-1996; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Georgia, M, 1938-1991 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Georgia, M, 1885-1995 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Georgia, M, 1851-1998; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Georgia, M, 1882-1987 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Georgia, M, 1841-1991 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Georgia, M, 1841-1987; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Georgia, N-O, 1815-1992 (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Georgia P-Q, 1857-1975; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Georgia, R, 1849-1973; Undated (Box 12 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Georgia, S, 1859-1975; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Georgia, S, 1832-1991 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Georgia, S, 1985 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Georgia, S, 1873-1985; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Georgia, T-V, 1833-1987; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Georgia, W, 1820-1982; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Georgia, W, 1906-1987 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Georgia, W-Y, 1850-1990; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Georgia, unidentified executions, 1867; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Georgia, multiple executions, 1882-1914; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Georgia, executions recorded in county histories, 1889-1995; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Georgia, executions recorded in regional histories, 1989 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Georgia, executions recorded in statewide records, 1887-1995; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Georgia, executions recorded in statewide records, 1938-1991; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Georgia, unconfirmed and possible executions, 1858-1990 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Hawaii, 1930-1946 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Idaho, A-S, 1901-1971; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Idaho, S-W, 1888-1994; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Idaho, multiple executions, 1887-1989 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Idaho, executions recorded in statewide records, 1976; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Illinois, A, 1933-1995 (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Illinois, B, 1878-1992; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 22)
    - Illinois, B, 1854-1997; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 23)
    - Illinois, B-C, 1873-1997; Undated (Box 13 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 24)
    - Illinois, C, 1907-1988 (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Illinois, C-D, 1856-1993; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Illinois, D, 1880-1995; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Illinois, D-F, 1880-1995; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Illinois, G, 1877-1994 (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Illinois, G, 1980-1994 (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Illinois, G, 1879-1988; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Illinois, G-H, 1824-1963; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Illinois, H-J, 1893-1991; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Illinois, J-k, 1919-1986; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Illinois, K-L, 1881-1975; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Illinois, L-M, 1837-1985; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Illinois, M-N, 1878-1997; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Illinois, N-P, 1894-1977; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Illinois, P, 1893-1993; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Illinois, R-S, 1899-1984; Undated (Box 14 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Illinois, S, 1933-1963; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Illinois, S, 1895-1990; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Illinois, S, 1913-1996; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Illinois, S-T, 1933-1951; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Illinois, T-W, 1881-1990; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Illinois, W, 1986-1991 (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Illinois, W, 1921-1996; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Illinois, W-Z, 1886-1995; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Illinois, unidentified and multiple executions, 1885-1995; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Illinois, multiple executions, 1912-1957; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Illinois, executions recorded in county histories, 1878-1994; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Illinois, executions recorded in statewide records, 1887; 1984; 1991; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Indiana, A-B, 1879-1983; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Indiana, B, 1886-1997; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Indiana, B-C, 1884-1997; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Indiana, C-F, 1826-1976; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Indiana, G-H, 1823-1976; Undated (Box 15 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Indiana, H-M, 1825-2001; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Indiana, M-R, 1822-1981 (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Indiana, R-S, 1838-1996 (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Indiana, S, 1876-1998; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Indiana, T-W, 1867-1985; Undated (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Indiana, multiple executions, 1936-1976 (Box 16 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)